{
    "subject": "resource/Claudio_Bieler",
    "predicate": "property/clubs",
    "object": "resource/LDU_Quito",
    "human_readable": "Claudio Bieler plays for LDU Quito.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7162767648696899,
            "question": "For which club does Claudio Bieler play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.677852213382721,
            "question": "What position does Claudio Bieler play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6695692539215088,
            "question": "What is the name of the team Claudio Bieler plays for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6094386577606201,
            "question": "Has Claudio Bieler played for any other teams?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48224136233329773,
            "question": "What league does LDU Quito play in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46493765711784363,
            "question": "Where does Claudio Bieler play his football?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4472450017929077,
            "question": "Is Claudio Bieler a football player?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41953369975090027,
            "question": "What is the nationality of Claudio Bieler?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2878446578979492,
            "question": "In which country is LDU Quito based?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24958203732967377,
            "question": "Is LDU Quito a successful football team?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Claudio Bieler plays for LDU Quito.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2629_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In which country is LDU Quito based?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2629_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the nationality of Claudio Bieler?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2629_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Claudio Bieler a football player?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2629_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2629_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2629_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2629_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2629_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2629_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2629_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2629_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2629_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2629_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2629_77.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nWhile the documents mention Claudio Bieler playing for LDU Quito in the past, they state he was transferred to Sporting Kansas City in 2013.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple \"Claudio Bieler plays for LDU Quito\" based on the provided context information:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents contain multiple mentions of Claudio Bieler playing for LDU Quito in Ecuador's Serie A, winning titles with the team, and achieving individual success while playing for LDU Quito. This confirms that the triple is supported by the information provided."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide multiple references to Claudio Bieler's playing career, including his time at LDU Quito. For instance, the document states, \"Bieler, an Argentina native who holds dual citizenship in Ecuador, has scored 57 goals in 110 league games for LDU Quito in Ecuador\u2019s Serie A and his 71 goals in 155 games in all competition for the club are the most in team history.\" This supports the statement that Claudio Bieler plays (played) for LDU Quito."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Multiple passages state he was *released* by Kansas City and signed with Belgrano, and that Sporting KC acquired him from LDU Quito.",
            "category": 1
        }
    }
}